[Music]
[音乐]
but since the final day but one
但自最后一天以来
to deepen futuristic
加深未来主义
making displays conference maybe you get
做展示会也许你会
the hunt for the last of energy
寻找最后的能量
conference on to talk about it brings
会议上谈论它带来的
is loud honking and who does not care
大声鸣喇叭，谁不在乎
can novatek consulting only
只能novatek咨询
people from germany we have round
来自德国的人们
two hundred and fifty employees and
250名员工和
maybe it consulting uk twitter
也许它咨询英国推特
mentally he is something in the session
在精神上他是会议中的一员
pavilion willi basic cybernetic
亭阁威利基本控制论
Introduction to need is love
介绍需要就是爱
who was in the session of my colleague
谁在我同事的会议上
matthias häusler next web will be back
matthiashäusler下一个网站将会回来
to compose the introduction second
第二篇作绪论
part wants beatles pink out loud
想要披头士乐队大声粉红色
pato shot thomas hogstedt works on the
帕托射击托马斯·霍格斯泰特作品
basics basically youtube city run
基本原理youtube city run
command what happens it is treated
命令发生什么情况
is peter deployment would have liked that
是彼得部署会喜欢的
deployment rowling update &amp; company to
部署罗琳更新和公司
install spot containing new yorker
安装包含纽约客的地点
container becomes obedient
容器听话
motto creating the players said and
创建球员的座右铭说和
services precedence balancing
服务优先级平衡
slip on jupiter invest in future
在木星上滑倒投资未来
applications world news to use your
应用世界新闻来使用您的
application isaaa basic concept of
应用isaaa的基本概念
companies republic a6 deployment
公司共和国a6部署
services and of course
服务，当然
speak about
谈论
jumps loud composed project one
跳大声组成的项目一
mainboard of dead is auto-conficker
死亡的主板是自动配置的
spring application and composed
Spring 申请和组成
[Music]
[音乐]
config maps from brasiliens you can
您可以从巴西配置地图
conficker your config maps such
混淆您的配置映射，例如
interviews in the property is you can so
可以在物业进行面试
be something like application properties
像应用程序属性一样
Mapping otherwise yes times format mapping
映射，否则是时间格式映射
as it used to be as a support community
因为它曾经是一个支持社区
project configuration is in progress
项目配置正在进行中
if not you can party
如果没有，你可以开派对
can do things really badly drawn like that
可以做这样的事情真的很糟糕
this sambel on victory what you here
这个胜利的三宝你在这里
the data is the basics tvn coach of
数据是电视的基础知识
important thing here is the four guys
重要的是这四个家伙
composed in dvz in secret
在dvz中秘密组成
Egypt so that there in plain text
埃及，以便在那里纯文本
basics values ​​inside the ecd database in
ecd数据库中的基本值
the control view
控制视图
important to protect its first secret
重要的是要保护它的第一个秘密
service attractive target for hackers
黑客服务有吸引力的目标
researcher system and architectures wants
研究者系统和架构想要
to steal your secrets the consequence of
窃取您的秘密的后果
can access data thick cars thiel vom
可以访问数据厚车thiel vom
you seek ways league too driven
你想办法联盟也有动力
logfiles you to cash is everywhere juana
您到处都是现金的日志文件
meet openly
公开见面
valletta least privilege prince always like that
瓦莱塔最低特权王子总是这样
so the sequence open up the door to
所以序列打开了通往
administration interface sometimes the
管理界面有时
hacker manages to get that i can
黑客设法使我可以
Property manager happens
物业经理发生
[Music]
[音乐]
best practice for success as well as in
成功的最佳实践以及
the company of documentation is with
文件公司在
sweet secrets of two dpa
两个dpa的甜蜜秘密
[Music]
[音乐]
basically open space antenna not
基本上没有开放空间的天线
intended for your client for juso infekt
为您的客户提供Juso感染
youcat access to the secrets from emergency
您从紧急情况中获取秘密
least privilege principle of the best
最佳的最小特权原则
practice for sequence in Chernobyl is
切尔诺贝利的顺序练习是
as pudding in warm weather like that
像这样在温暖的天气里的布丁
wall street
华尔街
but it is essential who is using
但谁在使用至关重要
environment mapping secrets of the
环境映射的秘密
danger of environment variables is the
环境变量的危险是
god in logfiles fps exception happening
日志文件中的上帝fps异常发生
from ampfing the Israelite lures
从增加以色列人的诱惑
logfiles if you can look in the logfiles
日志文件（如果可以查看日志文件）
the over staples that you short the
您做空的钉书钉
coated stepic is angles documentation
涂层阶梯是角度文档
Of course we have to advertise in Weimar
当然要在魏玛做广告
the volume mount so that willie
音量安装，以便威利
Sievers is William cryptic
Sievers是William的神秘主义者
has transported in the dvz in the looks
在外观上已在dvz中运输
it will be there in plain text in the oecd
它会以纯文本格式显示在OECD中
data base on composed user cloud
基于组合用户云的数据库
provider the job in the case that left
在离开的情况下提供工作
provider s secret pretty at west so
提供者的秘密在西方如此
the encrypted at the data longer so
加密的数据更长，所以
volumes dvd pretty enabled volumes
DVD漂亮的卷
also wanted so broad is application
还希望应用如此广泛
layer secrets in
层秘密
pretty dress new economists demo
漂亮的新经济学家演示
in front of the cosmopolitan cluster of
在国际大都会的前面
extremus but already google cloud
极值但已经谷歌云
howie sees it is to chapter pistor
豪伊看到这是章皮斯特
incident composed secrets the perks of
事件构成了秘密的特权
being called the giving you can skip to
被称为赠品，您可以跳过
think i really the possibility that take
认为我真的有可能
it in some time with the south dakota
在南达科他州的某个时间
the sequence in my company of the cluster
集群中我公司的顺序
or the skater composed cluster
或由溜冰者组成的集群
[Music]
[音乐]
josef in gerd wan features you can
约瑟夫·格尔德湾的特色
select what is called enable application
选择所谓的启用应用程序
layer 2 switches in peter quint delivers
Peter Quint的第2层交换机可提供
but the user offers paypal to select
但用户提供贝宝选择
again there just created the new
再次在那里刚刚创建了新的
fierce land so fast panicking scenes
凶猛的土地如此恐怖的场面
cryptic vip tickets for stucki has now
Sticki的神秘VIP门票现在有
automatically conficker tauss at the
会自动混淆金牛座
google cloud not dead space creating
谷歌云不是死空间创建
the application layer secrets basically
应用层基本上是秘密
skin networks is using envelope y
皮肤网络正在使用信封y
composed which is available
组成哪些可用
composed version one shot in what
组成版本一枪在什么
you can telegate the witcher 2
你可以用电传巫师2
ms provider ready at the user cloud
ms提供程序已在用户云上就绪
providers according to google usa appear
谷歌美国提供者出现
description language data encryption
描述语言数据加密
keys there in the cd data base in
cd数据库中的键位于
computer science camps the data of
计算机科学扎营的数据
secret service is back to the clubs
特勤局又回到了俱乐部
in klitzschen data and description
在klitzschen的数据和描述
actually goodwin is you can always
其实古德温是你可以永远
thought disk i
思想盘我
encrypted in klitzschen data cleansing
在klitzschen数据清理中加密
pretty how does cinema center storage cost
电影院存储的成本如何
components service in the cloud tms
云TMS中的组件服务
motives when composed in the disco
在迪斯科舞厅创作的动机
plans google cloud in except so prominently
计划将Google Cloud纳入其中
provider continued to believe support or the
提供者继续相信支持或
social award for example google cloud
社交奖，例如Google Cloud
So gms can you can setup magic of word
所以gms您可以设置单词魔术吗
access module like you do not want to buy
像您不想购买的访问模块
the specific provider as well as sap like came
具体的提供者以及树液一样来了
also a vehicle composed the
也是组成
stage soja understand the basics on the
阶段大 bean 了解的基础知识
sojus enemy the complete kotov
杀害敌人完整的科托夫
composed stuff present and github
组成的东西存在和github
but that is so far according to
但这到目前为止
providing the discovery client
提供发现客户端
politically so you can not discover other
政治上，所以你找不到其他
services composed by colin inside
科林内部组成的服务
with too hot support as well as hosting
过于热门的支持以及托管
cloud loadbalancer it new project sword
云负载均衡器it新项目剑
presented support to date I am
到目前为止，我已经提供了支持
cloud company of the car in the direction
汽车云公司的发展方向
of the spring cloud load balancing
云负载均衡
domain pawel jock day is is the
域帕克乔克天是
mapping on configuration maps spring
在配置图上映射Spring
according to composition, except mapping of
根据组成，除了
Sequence exposed project is so
序列暴露项目是如此
political system so even if your
政治制度，即使您
application wans locally and yang
应用程序在本地和杨
machine and if you are connected to your
机器，如果您已连接到
composed cluster in you have access
您可以访问组成的集群
to wait that brings out loud
等待那响亮的
application wants the economist config
应用程序需要经济学家配置
Maps of yorks is tested in clusters
约克地图在集群中进行了测试
oslo kelly more often conficker configuration
oslo kelly更经常混淆配置
to test so it is with locally in the
进行测试，以便与本地
configuration maps de dark
黑暗的配置图
composing cluster so good for now
组成集群，到目前为止非常好
testing debugging proxy server using
使用以下命令测试调试代理服务器
except the club anthem of the profile
除了个人资料的俱乐部国歌
review deployed inside composed
审查部署在内部组成
automatically puts his political
自动把他的政治
profile tv-special configuration of the uli
配置文件的电视特殊配置
hess as well as launches venue in co political
赫斯以及在合作政治中推出会场
a progressive song there is sexy lingerie
进步的歌声有性感的内衣
and work would moment what the islam one
和工作会瞬间伊斯兰的东西
version coming to the ex coworker
版本发布给前同事
offset people towards the end babbel der
将人们推向最后
and imports is authoritative potthoff
进口是权威
indicator tti europe online status of
欧洲tti欧洲指标在线状态
projects and what you need of that thing
项目以及您需要的东西
cloud company the project with the start
云公司从头开始的项目
of the discovery small right here for
在这里发现的小
startups support in alsmoos petersdorf
alsmoos petersdorf的初创企业支持
opencl 1.1 support
opencl 1.1支持
so you can choose what features the
因此您可以选择
superstar the twitter website should that
超级巨星推特网站应该
start up for old stuff at once
马上开始做旧的东西
it's the mother holly cluster but that
这是母亲冬青树丛，但那
Diploma is the lynx well set
文凭是天猫座
google cloud the provisioning
谷歌云供应
committee willi almost to google cloud
威利委员会差点到谷歌云
connect expo - so that must be photographer
连接博览会-必须是摄影师
basically user service application
基本上是用户服务应用
release in the exile of pons undoubtedly
毫无疑问地被放逐到了流放地
brink composed the application suite
边缘组成了应用程序套件
basic song david waters brings loud
基本歌曲大卫·沃特斯带来响亮的声音
Project
项目
[Music]
[音乐]
basically this is the user mapping used
基本上这是使用的用户映射
by using standard spring application like that
通过使用像这样的标准spring应用程序
young polio config maps added in warm
在温暖的环境中添加了年轻的小儿麻痹症配置图
twitter-user party do you have to bright
推特用户聚会你要亮吗
messages website message center config
消息网站消息中心配置
meppen tello spring comedian in you
梅彭·特莱 Spring 喜剧演员在你
the team is walking in the secret of the
团队正在秘密行动
secret of the environment mapping and
环境映射的秘密和
[Music]
[音乐]
Janecek
Janecek
look at the change configuration
看一下变更配置
here she cheers Medvedev and have the
她在这里为梅德韦杰夫欢呼，让
volume 1 gate secrets cni in wine and
第一卷门秘密在葡萄酒和
Waldviertel config meppen ii massa the
Waldviertel Config Meppen II Massa
from the händel slater and spring cloud
来自händelslater和 Spring 的云
computing cloud company the weather is
计算云公司的天气是
mapping on the victory red stuff that
映射到红色的胜利的东西
this mapreduce controller basically
这个mapreduce控制器基本上
jazz meets the message is fix on the
爵士遇见消息已修复
celebrate the end of the fair the styling
庆祝博览会的结束
as well as the basic rest controller print
以及基本的 rest controller 打印
outdoor confixx simple but many users
户外confixx简单但很多用户
the tales
故事
but now the figure is so united
但是现在这个数字是如此团结
Our user service will be dizzy
我们的用户服务会令人头晕
secret service providing the user name
提供用户名的秘密服务
the user password templates in saint omer
Saint omer中的用户密码模板
service to the youth password so you
服务青年密码，让您
see quite calls a car driver
看到相当叫车司机
usernamen basic song what are water den
用户名基本歌曲什么是水窝
USA builds in the deep password though
美国虽然建立了深密码
Siegfried Meister became the conficker
齐格菲·迈斯特（Siegfried Meister）
is is a basic input password
是基本输入密码
interface
接口
we can easily change the cote
我们可以轻松地更改棚
basics tv recorder should now be the
电视记录器的基本知识现在应该是
courtage ok tuscaloosa sorbet is the
好吧，tuscaloosa果汁冰糕是
new password if the plates too
如果车牌也输入新密码
composing is indeed burst of project
组成确实是项目的爆发
as well as helpers
以及助手
config map in jamaal format explorer
Jamaal格式资源管理器中的配置图
Switch will be so last time
上次切换会如此
we want the people and
我们希望人民和
composers as well as helpers them
作曲家以及他们的助手
consists of the username and squeeze
由用户名和压缩组成
password insight
密码洞察
almost a folder to connect especially that
几乎是一个要连接的文件夹
casting
铸件
a
一
Michael javascript calls it a challenge
迈克尔javascript称之为挑战
there is access that had to be under code
有访问权限必须在代码下
from
的
solid plaster is branching correctly
固体石膏正确分支
networks slovak the blue too
网络也变蓝了
conficker secrets and to compose
混淆秘密并撰写
a word as before half of you calls
一句话就像你们一半的人一样
komitees cloud projects the half
komitees云项目一半
conficker service account employee
Conficker服务帐户员工
good as conficker service account wifag
很好，作为Conficker服务帐户wifag
on coopers between based access
基于访问之间的库珀
control service pack texas to the lps of
将Service Pack德克萨斯州控制到LP的
Computing cloud company does it is
计算云公司做到了
required to configure service accounts
配置服务帐户所需
to get access to the different eps
获得对不同的EPS
composed tweets volksarmee the
组成推文volksarmee
config maps
配置图
[Music]
[音乐]
delivery service account that I call that
我称之为的送货服务帐户
hallows brings something funny, according to komikers
根据komikers的说法，圣殿带来了一些有趣的东西
is not like texas city found committees
不像德克萨斯市成立委员会
as well as basic access names spaces
以及基本访问名称空间
despite services endpoints in config maps
尽管配置映射中有服务端点
like basic access update creative as well
例如基本访问权限更新广告素材
the change and things to be careful
变化和注意事项
to privilege stresses without poisons
享受无毒的压力
cluster admin rights to your application
对您的应用程序的集群管理员权限
support idea.de binding calls as well as
支持idea.de绑定调用以及
the find here on services is loud
服务上的发现很大
coop an it is to work actually
合作，这实际上是工作
the service levels
服务水平
march there acts as though manning
进军那里似乎就像在配员
services between services creative load
服务之间的服务创意负载
balancing lethal excess of hello
平衡致命的打招呼
world service to get my criticism something like that
世界服务使我的批评之类的
like canon switzerland ag as well as staples
如佳能瑞士股份公司和钉书针
components checkout superstar twitter
组件结帐超级明星twitter
posting cloud application local
在本地发布云应用程序
Serbian basically configuration
塞尔维亚语基本配置
the company of the cluster but the danger
集群的公司，但是危险
that further login local user
进一步登录本地用户
locally violent juso secret
局部暴力的犹太秘密
tweets actually the conflict of the
推文实际上是
catch the cluster so you know tests
赶上集群，以便您了解测试
willi local folders config map work
威利本地文件夹配置映射工作
installed in your customer service in
安装在您的客户服务中
composed login like physio is ipos
像physio这样的组合登录是ipos
with suit and robots txt as well as josef
带有西装和机器人txt以及josef
3gs and offered to help out extended
3gs，并提供帮助扩展
help friend
帮助朋友
even the know we have no use of the
即使知道我们没有使用
state is departure like outside the 11th
像11号以外的州一样出发
a friend in the table to use a
桌子上的朋友使用
friend to see the hotmail.de
的朋友可以查看hotmail.de
service account of that conficker
该Conficker的服务帐户
urges pott to take the emergency and
敦促波特采取紧急措施，
The hosting basic as award is when you
主办基本奖是当你
before wanning composes second composed
万宁之前组成第二个
lok access the lok on the
乐享乐
sophie koser lockout songtitel such
sophie koser停工Songtitel这样
so looks like two studios of
所以看起来像两个工作室
conflict parties such know so
这样的冲突方知道
conficker stable organism the people
让人相信稳定的有机体
open again
再次打开
does he have that we have
他有我们有吗
too much information if we basically
如果我们基本上没有太多信息
knows exactly who is the youngest pilot
确切知道谁是最年轻的飞行员
Mechanisms on steam cloud computing
蒸汽云计算的机制
sofa is the plaster podium
沙发是石膏裙
so in the bütt treppchen if the user
因此在bütttreppchen中，如果用户
butt stepping offspring cloud the
屁股踩后代云
lingerie youtube conficker what has to be
女用贴身内衣裤youtube conficker必须是什么
piloten jumps composed like that
飞行员跳像这样组成
basically hotel is here is the t want
基本上酒店就在这里
to use the following config maps absolutely
绝对使用以下配置映射
basic print application to make it easy
基本的打印应用程序使其变得容易
ways to basics or config magix spring
基本方法或配置Magix Spring的方法
properties of us can say you can look like this
我们的属性可以说你可以看起来像这样
an apple of automatic as well as freising
一个自动和磨碎的苹果
on the config maps as well as change the
在配置图上以及更改
config map report will automatically
配置图报告将自动
user configuration last postbrief
用户配置最后一次发布
company of the basic so the silence is like
基本的公司，所以沉默就像
open to an update of the plaster from the
打开从石膏的更新
magic liu changer config is composed
魔术柳更换器配置组成
about folder to complete potsdam yukon
关于完成波茨坦育空地区的文件夹
quest people work now noordwijk
寻求人们现在工作noordwijk
at the end of ewz dpa now except
现在在ewz dpa结束时，
supported because it brings company
支持，因为它带来了公司
of the patrons disabled dpa and used volumes
禁用dpa和使用量的顾客
Mounted games for the secrets of the
安装游戏的秘密
aussie users to specify the mount point
澳大利亚用户指定安装点
often on the sequence in the spring cloud
经常在 Spring 的云层中
company of the trade audit for you
贸易审计公司为您服务
so almost immediately we two exactly
所以几乎立即我们两个
change actually won on politics
改变实际上在政治上赢得了胜利
Maps
地图
[Music]
[音乐]
the second most beautiful
第二美丽
weidmann sees the foma barcelona
魏德曼看到巴塞罗那的福马
02 clock update config map
02时钟更新配置图
on a lucky because hello barcelona
幸运的是，你好巴塞罗那
as well as kent update config map on the fly
以及即时更新kent更新配置图
and what does it prince prince about
王子呢？
jusos that would do well to update
很好的更新
confixx on the fly for spring valley usa
confixx在美国春谷飞翔
has julia child of spring to inch so
有 Spring 的朱莉娅孩子
part of the change and configuration and
更改和配置的一部分，以及
provide samson basic mechanisms too
也提供samson基本机制
update poppig understands except that
更新poppig可以理解，除了
loudly composes think we take
大声地认为我们
over that mechanisms something of the
在那种机制上
partner and config maps in sequence
伙伴和配置映射顺序
second started the discovery features
第二次启动发现功能
details pictures basic service as well
详细图片以及基本服务
swearing service net is the
宣誓服务网是
server side squeeze a small page
服务器端压缩一小页
the server in two servers weiher
两台服务器中的服务器
discovery client sees risks that is
发现客户看到的风险是
this using the discovery client
使用发现客户端
defined the user discovery small the
将用户发现定义为小
outer us is as loud as political
我们外部的声音和政治一样响亮
that must be klaut then klaut drive
那一定是klaut然后是klaut驱动器
the folgsame 4you take place
folgsame 4you发生了
jurica attorneys at discovery
发现的法理律师
services web client to be out of service
服务Web客户端停止服务
Active in the case modder on basic doing
积极参与基本的案件修改
a searching for fun service 151
搜寻娱乐服务151
once a service the basic second
一次服务基本秒
category customer service ducks just call
分类客户服务鸭子只叫
to get it with a web client
通过网络客户端获取
beck
招手
I was supposed to apply there for that
我应该在那里申请
hofer dear guests has to watch
亲爱的客人必须注意
so correct away from the number of service
所以要正确选择服务数量
as well as out of the stupidest
以及最愚蠢的
almost half of the people who swing
几乎有一半的人摇摆
service of apps like outside
外部应用程序的服务
Script the attraction services is coming soon
脚本吸引服务即将推出
boring special exists
无聊的特殊存在
because ford escort service accounts like
因为福特护航服务帐户
bed bath beyond services is called points
服务之外的床浴被称为积分
or config maps the brands costa jadson
或配置映射品牌哥斯达黎加杰德森
from discovery service interface as well
也来自发现服务界面
Do you have the service accounts and dandy
您有服务帐户和花花公子吗
boy special service
男孩特殊服务
so eva moves locally ii the substance off
所以eva将物质移到本地
hang question service to see what
挂问题服务，看看有什么
happens locally ii
发生在当地
that was just the answer you had
那只是你的答案
the old with question of live like that
老人这样的生活问题
number of domatter moment as well as two
domatter矩数以及两个
close to that sam and composer lent her
靠近那个山姆，作曲家借给了她
But he was so afraid now
但是他现在很害怕
people like them exactly how are they doing
人们喜欢他们到底他们怎么样
fear of which basically is the
担心基本上是
fear of service and case
担心服务和案件
so that is the fear in the form of
所以这就是恐惧的形式
dementia service as a kind of pressroom
痴呆症服务作为一种新闻发布室
the folders as well as for discovery client
文件夹以及发现客户端
support in defensive discovery
支持防御性发现
kleibrink loud and yet composed
kleibrink响亮而沉稳
No car was the discovery small in
没有车是在小发现
discover automotive services in politics
在政治中发现汽车服务
traffic lights except in my guitar propos too
交通灯，除了我的吉他道具
computer style business managers
计算机风格的业务经理
saturday composed security patch
星期六撰写的安全补丁
dress important community security like that
这样打扮重要的社区安全
the tanny fanny bad is creative like that
丹妮·范妮·巴德（Tanny fanny bad）就是那样的创造力
this the world as a peace project
这个世界是一个和平项目
happening so apologetically when
如此抱歉地发生
she comes is not really important that way
她来那不是很重要
this of projects dealer
这个项目经销商
Cybernetic outsourcing is marble
控制论外包是大理石
containers into production and we
容器投入生产，我们
have to security massive interviews in
必须进行大规模的采访
light stapled iller component wanning
钉书机组件
inside your composed cluster so the
在您组成的集群中
zvei helme piston root of companies of
zvei helme活塞根公司
the city helmet can do everything
城市头盔可以做任何事情
composed song the brink's home
创作的歌濒临的家
security picking inside should be composed
内部安全拣选应组成
the 2d picture helm tripolis first
先将2D图片掌舵Tripolis
alphaversion working component
alphaversion工作组件
rest in peace keeping up with the
安息，与时俱进
available switch to date on which may
可用的日期切换到
not the is novizenmeister details for
不是novizenmeister的详细信息
joker containers do it well when committees
小丑容器在委员会工作时做得很好
and folders news portal inside container
容器中的文件夹和文件夹新闻门户
can web pages
可以网页
[Music]
[音乐]
so now at dc the user detective in
所以现在在直流上，用户侦探
docker case saint wit joke of
码头工人案例圣人机智的笑话
berning so it rests conception politics
柏宁，使它停留在构想政治上
so to speed up yet
所以要加快
container ship it so that the body
集装箱船使身体
the context for pott is in container
Pott的上下文位于容器中
then as a partner for the dreams what
然后作为梦想的合作伙伴
you can auto is the post will be the
您可以自动将帖子发布为
Policewoman Beta in Extending Brivio Cloud
扩展Brivio Cloud的女警Beta
provider at the moment that you can not
您目前无法提供
use anydoc content access and the
使用anydoc内容访问和
context is the complete project
上下文是完整的项目
below the pott level and off restrictive
低于盆水平且不严格
in front of the container level the basic
在集装箱高度之前
lingy kravitz escalation any
lingy kravitz升级任何
more you down the privilege is so
越是让您失望，特权就是
if it lothar otto content access
如果它harthotto内容访问
whirls on the rich bonuses of the security
旋转着丰厚的证券红利
context in place and you say you can not
上下文到位，你说你不能
stop order of linux capabilities for
停止Linux功能的订购
four loko containers is the eu
四个loko容器是欧盟
so bitter from running in the box
如此苦涩
now violently specify user directive on
现在在以下位置猛烈地指定用户指令
you sing here to great image witches
你在这里唱歌给伟大的形象女巫
by ideas to less images are provided by
通过减少图片提供的想法
google the idea here is the display of the
谷歌的想法是这里的显示
images that and include any wall one
包含任何一幅墙的图像
linux-distribution soko boss of
linux-distribution soko的老板
Disqualification of the images are
失格的图像是
available for example the villa was in
可用，例如别墅在
the justin embers the minimum said that it
贾斯汀灰烬最低说
want to be quiet one java application so so
希望成为一个安静的Java应用程序，所以
know as anno hecker
知道作为安诺·赫克
sneak in interviews container using the
使用
shell anymore
壳了
one of the gangster image is besides much
黑帮形象之一是远远超过
smaller than the user one and the
小于用户一个和
distribution of context
语境分布
jfp way of poker images that have lots
jfp的扑克图像方式很多
of mobility insights as or prominently
流动性见解
once like no change in this report of
就像本报告的不变
2009 instruments ti has samsung 6 and
2009年TI的仪器有三星6和
must come stalker images if all those
如果所有这些都必须来跟踪图像
stalker images have lots on was up to
缠扰者的图像有很多
top floor base images you use he is
您使用的顶层基本图像是
a prominent recently people that are
最近杰出的人
using alpine director willi space image
使用高山导演威利空间图像
provider cicek which this image of duty
提供者cicek这形象的责任
cost universe all have sex with any
成本宇宙都与任何人发生性关系
password safe out any password checking
密码安全，可进行任何密码检查
so in bed is packed with something called for
所以在床上挤满了需要
leave like here in side
像这边一样离开
I'm cloud computing on josef picture
我在josef图片上进行云计算
the open source software update you need
您需要的开源软件更新
is cluster stock exchanges and the province of
是集群证券交易所和
manager believes pioneer is in short supply
经理认为先驱短缺
which save up to date notes or apps and
保存最新的笔记或应用程序，以及
updates on car way or update images
更新行车方式或更新图片
and space images
和空间图像
images on Father's Day cloud computing
父亲节云计算中的图像
environment vce
环境vce
you can easily consequence the car came
您可以轻松地推断出汽车来了
in spring cloud computing has become so mushroom
在 Spring ，云计算变得如此迅速
is the ears of helmut Werner's insight
是Helmut Werner洞察力的耳朵
hybrid is done for security check
混合完成安全检查
using the least privilege for service
使用最少特权进行服务
The last one enters with winkler
最后一个与winkler一起进入
Communication brings company does not
沟通带来的公司不
the words with service accounts n roll
带有服务帐户的单词n roll
swing clarinetist recognize as in the profession
摇摆单簧管家公认专业
Aunt documentation looks like it will
阿姨的文件看起来像
good ice already have easy forex
好冰已经容易外汇
in google cloud to eclipse audio secrecy
在Google Cloud中使音频保密性黯然失色
automatically
自动
because except say no go too good
因为除了说不走得太好
composed bio components container
组成的生物成分容器
images up to date so that basically or
图片，以便基本上或
hotels
酒店
still growing
还在增长
ok then embodied
好然后体现
[Applause]
[鼓掌]
[Music]
[音乐]